Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Writings and Speeches, 1912-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Open Files, 1912-1993 and undated
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (19-27 of 112 folders) (Box 17)
    - 1954. 16.6. Speech. America's Dynamic Economy Offers Expansion Opportunities for the Drug Trade in 1954-55 (Box 17)
    - 1954. 16.7. Speech. Change to a Consumption Economy Challenges Marketing (Box 17)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (28-35 of 112 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.8. Article. Aggressive Selling Can Turn the Tide. National Sales Executive News, April (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.9. Speech. Selling--the Key to Sustained Prosperity (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.10. Speech. Consumption Viewpoint on Consumer Credit (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.11. Article. Magic of Consumption Opportunity for an Immediate 10% Increase in Sales. Advertising Age, Market Data Issue, May 3 (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.12. Speech. What’s Ahead for Business? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.13. Speech. What's Ahead for Business? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.14. Speech. What's Ahead for Business? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.15. Speech. What's Ahead for Business? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.16. Speech. Question Marks in the Economy (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.17. Speech. Change to a Consumption Economy Challenges Advertising (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.18. Speech. Change to a Consumption Economy Challenges Salesmanship (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.19. Speech. What's Ahead for Business? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.20. Speech. What's Ahead for the Power Lawn Mower Business? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 16.21. Client talk. Owens Illinois Glass. How Market for Tableware Glass Increased by Income--1941 (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.1. Speech. What's Ahead for Business in 1955? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.2. Speech. Sales Opportunities from the Viewpoint of the Economist (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.3. Speech. Higher Standard of Living--Your Key to Future Prosperity (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.4. Article. Memo to Americans: New Age of Promise Ahead! Family Weekly Magazine, Aug.29 (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.5. Client talk. United States Brewers Foundation. Visualization of Crossley Nationwide Survey of Beer & Ale Consumption; the People's Choice (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.6. Client talk. United States Brewers Foundation. Supplementary report derived from regional tabulations of Crossley survey (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.7. Speech. What's Ahead for the Furniture Industry? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.8. Speech. What's Ahead for Business in 1955? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.9. Speech. New Opportunities and Economic Change (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.10. Speech. Changing Standards of Living That Will Affect Markets for Photographic Products (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.11. Speech. Consumption Viewpoint on Consumer Credit (Box 18)
    - 1954. 17.12. Speech. What's Ahead for Business in 1955? (Box 18)
    - 1954. 18.1. Speech. Business Outlook and Your Business (Box 18)
    - 1954. 18.2. Other writing. Huge New Markets (booklet) (Box 18)
    - 1954. 18.3. Speech. Business Outlook for 1955 (Box 18)
    - 1954. 18.4. Speech. Opportunities for Expansion in Sales 1955 (Box 18)
    - 1954. 18.5. Speech. What's Ahead for Business in 1955? (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.6. Speech. What's Ahead for Business in 1955? (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.7. Speech. Huge New Markets (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.8. Speech. Opportunities for Expansion in Sales in 1955 (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.9. Speech. Quick Look at 1955 (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.10. Speech. What's Ahead for Your Business in 1955 (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.11. Speech. What's Ahead for Business (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.12. Client talk. Seven-Up Company. Letter and charts sent to John T. Tabor (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.13. Speech. Influence on Our Economy of the Trend Toward Family Life (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.14. Client talk. Eastman Kodak. Starch Analysis of Kodak Commercials and Attitude Toward Norby Program (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.15. Speech. Sales and Prospects for the Coming Year (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.16. Speech. Job for Advertising in the Continuing Expansion of Our National Economy (Box 18)
    - 1955. 18.17. Speech. Economic Trends That Can Expand Hosiery Sales (Box 18)
    - 1955. 19.1. Article. $40 Billion More Sales by 1956 Essential. Advertising Age, Market Data Issue, May 16 (Box 18)
    - 1955. 19.2. Speech. Size and Potential of International Markets Over the Next 25 Years International Advertising Association (Box 18)
    - 1955. 19.3. Speech. Decision in the Markets (Box 18)
    - 1955. 19.4. Speech. General Outlook for Business (Box 18)
    - 1955. 19.5. Client talk. Florida Citrus Commission. Charts used in 1955 presentation (Box 18)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (36-45 of 112 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.6. Speech. Economy of 1960 (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.7. Article. Annual Food Sales of $96 Billion Deemed Possible in 10 Years. Food Business, July (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.8. Client talk. United States Brewers’ Association. Economic Consequences of Proposed Regulation (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.9. Speech. Huge New Markets (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.9a. Letter. To: Mr. G. L. Howard, Advertising Manager, Elgin National Watch Company, re: jewelers talk (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.10. Speech. Changing Standards of Living That Point to Expanding Opportunity for the Furniture Industry (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.11. New Business. Anheuser Busch. Charts used for New Business presentation (Box 19)
    - 1955. 19.12. Client talk. Eastman Kodak. Charts: Indicated Influence of Kodak TV Programs on Picture-Taking; Indicated Influence of Kodak TV Programs on Kodak Film Purchases (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.1. Speech. Your Marketing Outlook (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.2. Speech. Sales and Prospects for the Coming Year (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.3. Client talk. Scott Paper Company Sales Meeting. Greatest Future in History (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.4. Client talk. J.B. Williams Company. Charts prepared for C.T. Lipscomb’s use as a panelist at NARD meeting in October (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.5. Speech. Outlook for Business in General (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.6. Speech. Marketing Outlook for 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.7. Speech. $40 Billion More Sales in 1956? (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.8. Speech. Job For. Advertising in the Continuing Expansion of Our National Economy (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.9. Speech. Look Ahead for Business (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.10. Speech. Advertisings' Job in the Continuing Expansion of Our Economy (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.11. Client talk. Aluminium Limited Sales Conference (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.12. Speech. More Prosperity or a Downswing? (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.13. New Business. Steinway & Sons (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.14. Speech. Marketing Outlook for 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.15. Speech. Consumer Markets: How Much Spending? How Much Saving? (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.16. Speech. Look Ahead for Business (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.17. New Business. General Mills. Details re: AHJ participation in meeting (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.18. Speech. What's Ahead for Business (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.19. Article. Living Standards Must Be Taught. Challenge Magazine, Dec. (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.20. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. Summary of comments and charts used at meeting (Box 19)
    - 1955. 20.21. Speech. Minnesota Mining & Mfg. Company. Details re: AHJ participation in meeting (Box 19)
    - 1956. 20.22. Letter. To: Mr. Norman Strouse, re: Projections of advertising volume to parallel 1960 and 1965 opportunity (Box 19)
    - 1956. 20.23. New Business. R.K.O. Comments by AHJ: Economic Trends That Can Be to the Advantage of a Motion Picture Producer (Box 19)
    - 1956. 20.24. Article. 1956-1965 a $40 Billion Boom? Iron Age, Jan. 5 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 20.25. Speech. Sales Outlook 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.1. Speech. Economic Outlook for the Grocery Business (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.2. New Business. Van Camp Seafood Company. Details re: AHJ participation in solicitation for LAO (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.3. Client talk. Wool Bureau. Memo re: Names attending presentation; and charts used (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.4. Client talk. Seven-Up Company Letter to John T. Taber, re: Soft drink consumption per capita related to change in per capita disposable income (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.5. Client talk. Davoe and Raynolds Company Inc. Details re: AHJ participation in meeting (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.6. New Business. Burlington Mills--Hosiery. Details re: AHJ participation in meeting (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.7. Speech. Sales Outlook 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.8. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. Memo to Guy Mitchell re: Measure of the expanded potential for air travel that might result from fares 20-25% under present tourist fares (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.9. Speech. Business Outlook and Bank Public Relations Opportunities (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.10. Speech. Dairy Sales Outlook for 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.11. Speech. Economic Outlook for 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.12. Speech. Sales Outlook 1956 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.13. Speech. Keeping Tabs on the Explosive American Economy (speech was cancelled) (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.14. Letter. To: John Willem (JWT Chicago), re: California Cattle Feeders Association (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.15. Speech. Marketing in an Expanding Economy (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.16. Speech. Sales Outlook 1956--Keeping Tabs on the Explosive American Market (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.17. Speech. Today's Plan--Selling and Merchandising (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.18. Speech. What the Challenge to America Means to the Textile Industry (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.19. Speech. Sales Outlook 1956--Keeping Tabs on the Explosive American Market (Box 19)
    - 1956. 21.20. Other writing. Summary of Remarks Before the AAAA Int'l. Meeting (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.1. Article. Slowdown of Business Growth Disturbing and Unnecessary. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, May 7 (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.2. Speech. Job for Advertising in the Continuing Expansion of Our National Economy (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.3. Speech. Managements, Challenge in an Expanding Economy (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.4. Discussion. Increasing Consumption--the Key to an Expanding Prosperous Economy (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.5. Speech. Economic Outlook (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.6. Speech. Economic Outlook for the 1960s (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.7. Speech. What the Challenge to America Means to the Tufted Textile Industry (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.8. Speech. Economic Guideposts to Changing Your Marketing Plans (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.9. Speech. Today's Plan--Selling and Merchandising (Box 19)
    - 1956. 22.10. Letter. To: Edgar B. Mooney, Jr., Bates Fabrics Incorporated, re: Consumer expenditures for clothing & accessories (Box 19)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (46-55 of 112 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.11. Client talk. Francis I. du Pont. Some Economic Changes That Mean Opportunity (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.12. Letter. To: Charles A. McQueeney, Jr., New England Confectionery Company, re: Background data on which 1954 Was Low chart was based (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.13. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. Memo to: Milton S. Eisenhower, Jr. re: Projection of spending units by disposable income (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.14. Speech. Place of Industry in Our Society (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.15. Letter. To: John L. Van Zant (JWT Chicago) re: Meat Promotion Committee (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.16. Speech. Outlook for Economic Expansion and Increased Sales (Box 20)
    - 1956. 22.17. New Business. Beef Council (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.1. Speech. Economic Guideposts to Changing Your Marketing Plans (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.2. Speech. Job for Advertising--Expanding Consumption to Match Productive Ability (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.3. Speech. Today's Plan--Selling and Merchandising (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.4. Speech. Factors of a Growing Market Affecting Blue Cross and Blue Shield (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.5. Speech. Changing Patterns of Distribution in the Food Industry (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.6. Article. Consumers Hold 'Master Key' to Prosperity. New York Herald Tribune, Harvey Runner column, Oct. 7 (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.7. Speech. Economic Guideposts to Changing Your Marketing Plans (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.8. Article. 10% Greater Sales Opportunity in 1957--Needs 10% Greater Sales and Advertising Effort. Sales Management (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.9. Article. 'Velocity' Termed New Dimension to Reckon with in U. S. Economy--by Mr. Norman Strouse. New York Herald Tribune, Oct. 19 (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.10. Speech. Economic Guideposts to Changing Your Marketing Plans (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.11. Speech. Economic Optimism with A. Factual Handle (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.12. Speech. Business Forecasts Affecting Puerto Rico (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.13. Speech. Economic Reasons Why We Can Sell More (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.14. Speech. Pharmaceutical Industry & Tomorrow's Market (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.15. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. Comments made at sales meeting (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.16. Client talk. Crompton-Richmond sales meeting (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.17. Other writing. How Expenditures for Radios & TV Sets Increased (table) (Box 20)
    - 1956. 23.18. Speech. Economic Guideposts to Changing Your Marketing Plans (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.1. Speech. Economic Reasons Why We Can Sell More (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.2. Speech. Opportunity for Expansion of Meat Sales (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.3. Client talk. Raisin Advisory Board. Talk based on Wilmington S.E.C. Talk (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.4. Speech. Knowing the Customer (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.5. New Business. Safeway Stores. Based on Wilmington S.E.C. Talk (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.6. Speech. Forecast of the Future (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.7. Speech. Sales Outlook 1957-58 (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.8. Client talk. Francis I. du Pont. Talk based on National Association of Purchasing Agents (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.9. Client talk. Pan American World Airways. Talk before Regional Conference. (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.10. Speech. Consumer Credit Expansion Potential (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.11. Speech. Marketing in an Expanding Economy (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.12. Speech. Sales Outlook 1957-58 (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.13. Speech. Future for American Agriculture (Box 20)
    - 1957. 24.14. Client talk. American Bankers Association (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.1. Speech. Economic Reasons Why We Can, and Must, Sell More (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.2. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.3. Speech. Meeting of JWT Chicago people (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.4. Client talk. Libby McNeill & Libby. General presentation (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.5. Speech. What Are You Goint to Do about It? (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.6. Speech. Economic Reasons Why We Can, and Must Sell More (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.7. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.8. Letter. Suggested letter for Mr. Wm. Wright to Send to Mr. E. F. Altmaier, Mgr. Textile Fibers Division, E. I. du Pont (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.9. Article. Why Marketing Men Need More Consumer Credit Now. Printers’ Ink, May 10 (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.10. Speech. Opportunity for Expansion of Beef Sales (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.11. Letter. To: Arthur Porter, re: Outlook for the building market (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.12. Article. U.S. Living Standard Must Jump 50% by 1967. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, Apr. 29 (Box 20)
    - 1957. 25.13. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow--What Are You Going to Do about It? (Box 20)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (56-64 of 112 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.1. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.2. Other writing. Furniture Expenditures Can Expand Rapidly (table) (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.3. Letter. To: Samuel Meek, re: Some implications of Interurbia (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.4. Speech. Business Outlook for the Next 10 Years and Its Relationship to Newspaper Advertising (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.5. Speech. Packaging for a Changing Market (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.6. Article. Opportunity for Expansion of Beef Sales. Hereford Journal (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.7. Speech. Remarks at press conference on Western European markets; charts used by Dr. Reed Washington (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.8. New Business. Suchard. Meeting with Mr. Bossart (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.9. Client talk. Eastman Kodak. Suggested Introduction for booklet (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.10. Client talk. Francis I. Du Pont. Short talk before du Pont trainee group (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.11. Client talk. American National Red Cross. Income Per Capita from Annual Fund Campaign (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.12. Letter. To: William McKeehan; re: How density of population affects market for gasoline (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.13. New Business. Textile industry promotion (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.14. Article. Blueprint for Tomorrow--10 Year Opportunity--$650 Billion Production & $10 Billion Retail Drug Store Sales Possible. Drug Topics, Centennial issue, Nov. (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.15. Letter. To: Maurice Hanson, re: Aug. 29 letter from Holgar Johnson (Box 21)
    - 1957. 26.16. Client talk. Scripto meeting (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.1. Speech. Consumption Must Expand 50% by 1958 (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.2. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.3. Speech. Economic and Social Trends That Can Expand Markets for Photographic Products (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.4. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.5. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow--Opportunities for Expanding Retail Drug Store Sales (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.6. Speech. Our Food Sales Potential (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.7. Client talk. Rowntree Company Limited. Meeting and talk (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.8. Speech. School of Advanced International Studies (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.9. Speech. Impact of Discretionary Consumer Spending on the Economy (Box 21)
    - 1957. 27.10. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow--What Are You Going to Do about It? (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.1. Client talk. New Holland. Annual sales meeting (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.2. Speech. Trends in Consumer Buying Habits, Disposable Income and Future Consumption Rates (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.3. Client talk. Thomas A. Edison Industries. Potentials for Voicewriter and of Economy (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.4. Speech. Velocity of Change in Our Markets and Population (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.5. Speech. Role of Advertising in Our National Economy--Expanding Consumption to Match Productive Ability (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.6. Letter. Ford Motor Company. Letter to: Ben Donaldson (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.7. Client talk. Eastman Kodak Company. What's Ahead for Business (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.8. Speech. Same Significant Factors Influencing the Client--Future Growth of Gravure (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.9. Letter. Scott Paper Company Letter to Thomas B. McCabe (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.10. Speech. Economy of 1958-59 (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.11. Letter. To: Maurice Hanson, re: Letter from Clark C. Hambley of Matchabelli (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.12. Article. Selling Ourselves Out of a Slump. Broadcasting Magazine, Feb. 24 (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.13. Speech. Economic Outlook for Shopping Centers in 1958-59 (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.14. Speech. 10 Year Growth Opportunities (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.15. Speech. Talk on Economy--Including Habit Lag in Cosmetics (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.16. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow (Box 21)
    - 1958. 28.17. Speech. Opportunity for Expanding Sales of Life Insurance (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.1. Speech. Canadian Markets (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.2. Speech. What's Ahead for the American Economy (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.3. Article. $28 Billion Backlog of Consumer Demand Can Jump Sales 10% by 1959. Advertising Age, Market Data issue, May 5 (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.4. Client talk. Sylvania, Meeting Board Room at Sylvania (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.5. Letter. To: Mr. Stanley Resor, re: Some thoughts on current economic situation (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.6. Other writing. Postwar History Shows Greatest Inflation in Years of Gov't. Surplus-Least Inflation in Years of Deficit (table) (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.7. Speech. What's Ahead for the American Economy (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.8. Speech. What's Ahead for the American Economy (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.9. Client talk. Johns Manville. Talk on current economic situation (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.10. Client talk. Elgin Watch Company. Off-cuff talk with Elgin executives (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.11. Speech. Scientific Marketing (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.12. Speech. Food Business of the Future (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.13. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 21)
    - 1958. 29.14. Speech. Consumption Must Expand 50% by 1968 (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Arno (continued), (65-73 of 112 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1958. 29.15. Letter. To: Mr. Norman Strouse, re: Future opportunities for Pacific Northwest (Box 22)
    - 1958. 29.16. Speech. Outlook for the Economy in 1958-59 (Box 22)
    - 1958. 29.17. Other writing. Challenge of Our Economy. AHJ views as well as six other economists. Printers Ink, May 16 (interview) (Box 22)
    - 1958. 29.18. Speech. Consumption Must Expand 50% by 1968 (Box 22)
    - 1958. 29.19. Letter. To H. F. Guenin, Jr. (JWT Chicago); re: Mattress figures (Box 22)
    - 1958. 29.20. Speech. Growth of Our National Economy Will Expand Southern Markets Rapidly (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.1. Speech. Economics of a Fast Moving Age (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.2. Speech. Economics of a Fast Moving Age (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.3. Speech. Customer's Utopia of Tomorrow (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.4. Client talk. Elgin National Watch Company. The Economics of a Fast Moving Age (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.5. Other writing. Key importance of Growth (table) (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.6. Speech. Food Business of the Future (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.7. Speech. Economic and Social Trends That Point to Growth Opportunity for the Music Industry (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.8. Letter. To: S. W. Meek, re: Projections of foreign travel expenditures to 1967--could grow to exceed $6 billion in 10 yrs. (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.9. Client talk. Stouffer Corporation. Outlook for the Food Industry (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.10. Speech. Economic Outlook (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.11. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.12. Letter. To: S. W. Meek, re: Pan American, transatlantic fares (Box 22)
    - 1958. 30.13. Speech. Opportunity Is Yours (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.1. Article. Schlitz Brewing Company. Good Year for Quality Products (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.2. Speech. Status of Our Economy Today and Tomorrow (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.3. Speech. Economic Outlook (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.4. Speech. Growing Importance of Advertising in Our American Economy (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.5. Client talk. Schlage Lock Company. Talk based on Ebasco (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.6. New Business. Pacific Gas & Electric; Fuller Paint Company. Talks based on Ebasco (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.7. Speech. Is the Recession Receding? Town Hall (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.8. Speech. $30 Billion Backlog of Consumer Demand Awaiting Activation by Advertising (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.9. Speech. Opportunities for Market Expansion (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.10. Speech. Food Business of the Future (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.11. Speech. Threefold Expansion of Foreign Travel in 10 Years: Over $61 Billion Possible by 1969 (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.12. Client talk. McGraw-Edison. Talk based on Ebasco (Box 22)
    - 1958. 31.13. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.1. Speech. Economic Changes That Mean New Markets (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.2. Speech. How Rising Standards of Living Can Expand Markets and Trade (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.3. Speech. Food Business of the Future (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.4. Speech. Economic Guideposts for Milk Merchandising (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.5. Speech. Blueprint for Tomorrow (Box 22)
    - 1958. 32.5a. Letter. To: N. Strouse, re: 1959-60 opportunities for growth in business (Box 22)